Wow!
I-I don't usually show this to anyone
outside of my family, so...
My apologies!
This scene's giving me déjà vu.
No, we're sorry for imposing on you.
Ninjas sure are cool, though!
Though I may call myself a ninja,
I'm nowhere near as talented as my brother.
And my techniques really aren't
as amazing as they seem.
If anything, I'd rather not
have these abilities.
I often think how things would be
if only I'd been born "normal."
I-I understand that feeling well.
I, too, wish to be normal,
though I'm still trying to figure out
what "normal" means to me.
If I were able to discuss such things
with you, Ms. Naka...
I think it would really put my heart at ease.
R-Right! Of course!
I also specialize in throwing weapons, but...
Wow! I'd love to see you in action!
It's somewhat calming,
watching them interact like that.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
It seems like you've taken
another step toward your dream
of forming a harem, my dear Hitoyoshi!
What?!
Surrounding yourself with so
many cute girls... Oh, my...
You're certainly spoiled for choice!
N-No, no, no! You've got it all wrong!
It's nothing like that!
First, you're a no-show at the festival,
and now you appear out of nowhere?
Episode 10: You and the Forbidden Fruit.
Beautiful women come and go
like the wind, okay?
Ms. Nitta...?
Oh, is feeling my breasts pressed
against you from behind not enough?
Go ahead. Cop a squeeze.
Huh. I meant to throw it at the tree.
Don't subconsciously aim for the kill!
What are you, some kind of automaton?!
You got this!
Don't forget that you've asked me
to research your little sister for you!
Master Hitoyoshi, my apologies
for surprising you like that.
No, I'm okay.
She did it so subconsciously
that she feels no remorse, I see.
As I thought, Ms. Nitta, you're...
not a normal person either, are you?
Um, I'm Hikage...
The youngest daughter
of the Hikage clan, right?
Y-You know who I am?!
Well, I am an informant, after all.
What's more...
I also know that you were the one
who wrote Yuki's name on her test.
O-Oh?!
Don't aim consciously for the kill, either!
I see she's added another thing
she wants to protect to her list.
By the way, why exactly
are you here, Ms. Grace?
Oh, right.
I'm gonna be in China for a bit for work.
I was thinking if I asked
Xue's old acquaintances,
I might be able to get some
information on her sister.
Asking the organization directly
would be too risky, so...
It's basically your old stomping ground, right?
Not really... I didn't know
anyone besides my mentor.
Hmm...
Well, that's why I stopped by.
It's a shame I can't spend
Christmas with you guys, but...
be sure to have plenty of hot,
steamy nights with Hitoyoshi.
Steam?
Could you please not say
absurd things before you go?!
My old stomping ground, huh...
Um, I've been wondering... Are you two...
i-in a relationship?
What?!
S-Sorry! This is my first time trying
to engage in "girl talk"!
If that was the wrong moment
to bring it up, I'm very sorry!
After all, you are cousins, right?
Hold up! Like I said before, there's
really nothing like that between us.
Oh, really? I...
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
Ah! I'm sorry, too!
I've been watching you two for ages, and I
always thought you made the perfect couple...
W-We really aren't a couple!
And the whole premise is wrong, anyway!
Ms. Yuki and I are...
You know?
Ms. Yuki?
Being asked about my old acquaintances
made me remember.
I was just thinking how I've never
had anyone interested in me,
and nor have I been
interested in anyone before.
Being alone was enough.
But now...
It's fun adding more people
I want to protect into my life.
Yeah, I can see that.
Ms. Yuki's feelings are what you'd
call familial love, in a way.
It's snowing...
Dad
I'll be back in Japan
for the new year.
Whoa!
I know, right?
Snow really does get you excited, doesn't it?!
Now you're iced mochi!
All right, then! Me, too!
Here! A mini-snowman!
We don't get much snow here,
so when I was a child, I used to make
small snowmen like this.
Then I shall also...
It turned out a bit awkward.
No, it's very you, Ms. Yuki.
How should I put it...
The way it's doing its best
to be round reminds me of you.
Master Hitoyoshi...
Huh? Whoa!
Agemochitaro?!
Ah! M-My...
You've been real naughty lately, Mochita.
I-Is there any way to revive it...?
I think it's beyond saving, Ms. Yuki.
Sorry. I have to answer this.
Okay...
Yeah. Yeah, I know.
Oh, no, that's...
Yeah... I understand.
I'll have Riko tell Mom.
Bye.
It's already that time of year, huh...
Sorry, Ms. Yuki.
I need to go see Riko, so could you
watch the house for me?
Understood.
Um... Master Hitoyoshi...
It's cold!
She said she wanted to meet me
on the way home,
but does that mean she wants
to eat out tonight?
It's Christmas, so everywhere's
gonna be packed...
Why's it so crowded over there?
Master Hitoyoshi!
Wh-Why are you dressed like that?
I mean, it's normal, but...
I thought you'd be cold,
so I kept this scarf warm for you.
Are you a Sengoku warlord?
I mean, if we do this on Christmas,
it's almost as if...
Yes.
Let us go on a "date."
D-D-Da—
A date?! But why?
Ms. Riko advised me that you would feel better
if I were to go on this "date" with you.
While you were out, I received a phone call,
and she told me that you have some concerns
weighing on your mind at present.
In addition, you seemed
somewhat gloomy earlier,
and at that moment I wished
I could do whatever I could
to lighten your mood, even if only a little.
As long as your face is clouded over,
I also cannot become the
round snowman I wish to be.
Ms. Yuki... Uh...
If that's the case, then...
shall we continue our date?
I'd love to!
Um, should we keep holding hands?
Yes. Ms. Riko told me not to let go.
Oh, man.
I can almost see Riko's triumphant face.
It may be unavoidable,
but part of me just doesn't sit right
with seeing Ms. Yuki in that way.
To me, Ms. Yuki feels like...
a baby in an adult's body, in a way.
Katsuda's Sauce:
For a Healthy, Growing Child
*Please do not feed sauce to infants!
Goo-goo-ga.
Besides, even if I did feel
that way about her,
the relationship we have right now would be...
Master Hitoyoshi, where shall we go?
Huh? Uh...
Let's start with dinner, I guess.
Oh, it's snowing again.
Master Hitoyoshi, are you cold?
I'm fine.
I have this scarf, after all.
Oh, over there.
When the snow falls onto the lights,
it blurs them and makes them sparkle even more.
I just love seeing that.
That's another reason why I love the snow.
Huh? Did I say something weird?!
No...
I was just happy to hear you say
you loved me, Master Hitoyoshi.
I know you were only referring
to my namesake, but...
It felt good to hear it anyway.
Huh?
Huh?!
Let's decide what clothes you're going to wear
A Few Hours Ago
on your Christmas date
before Big Brother gets back!
Riko
If I remember correctly, you bought
a loose knitted cardigan, didn't you?
You have a great figure,
so you'd totally slay in something
that emphasizes your curves, but...
A more innocent look
works for Christmas, too!
If we're going with that,
you should pair it with a tight skirt,
along with a camisole that
goes with the knitted top.
A loose cardigan...
More innocent...
Tight skirt...
Camisole...
Your neck's still a bit bare, though...
My neck... I do have my bell...
Oh! That's right!
I think a choker would work great!
Riko
Then let down your hair and
fix it in place with a pin...
And we bought a handbag, too, didn't we?
Better bring that, as well.
I believe that would be this.
And for your legs, tights with matching boots!
Will dressing like this help lift
Master Hitoyoshi's spirits?
Yeah, absolutely!
Dad's House
In fact, you'll be casting a spell on him
filled with the magic of Christmas!
Show him an even more gorgeous side
of you than what he sees every day...
and send him head over heels for you!
Head over heels...
Understood.
I'll do my best to be even more beautiful in
his eyes than the snow he named me after!
Oh, man!
I only wish you could have heard her, too!
Ms. Yuki's just too adorable!
Oh... I see.
I really didn't want to hear that right now.
Besides... Do you really think
Ms. Yuki is the kind of person
who'd ever have romantic feelings for anyone?
I can't even imagine it.
But, you know, if we say my affection rating
for you is somewhere in the thirties...
Ms. Yuki's is probably over
a thousand, don't you think?
Okay, but why is yours so low?
And maybe that's why
she hasn't realized them yet!
Her feelings of romance!
Given how she wants to be with you forever,
isn't that basically love already?
Just thinking that you want
to be with someone... is love?
If you're that concerned,
How does the person you like feel about you?
Unrequited Love Diagnostic Test
Q1. Do they touch you physically?
Ta-dah! Take this Unrequited Love
Diagnostic Test!
Huh?
With this, we can see just how high
of a position you hold in her heart!
I don't think an online test is very reliable.
Oh, no, these things are spot on!
My friend used one of these to decide
whether to confess her love,
and she got exactly the result
she was hoping for!
That's just a coincidence.
Now, now, you've got nothing
to lose by trying it!
Let's go to our first question.
Does she touch you physically?
Does hand-to-hand count? Yes, I guess.
How does the person you like feel about you?
Unrequited Love Diagnostic Test
Q2.
Question 2. Does she praise you often?
Yes...
Question 3. Does she actively
initiate conversation with you?
Yes. We do live together.
Question 4. Does she help you
when you're in trouble?
Yes...
Question 5. Do your eyes suddenly meet?
Question 6. Does she often laugh
at the stories you tell?
Yes...
The next one is the last one.
Question 25.
Has she ever told you she likes you,
outside of a love confession?
I was just happy to hear you say
you loved me, Master Hitoyoshi.
N-No.
Okay! The results are out!
How does the person you like feel about you?
Unrequited Love Diagnostic Test
The chance of you getting together
with said person is...
There's a 96% chance that you both
have feelings for each other!
You're just going to have
to confess your love to her!
At 96%, you're basically a couple already!
She just says whatever she wants, huh?
It's the remaining 4% that I'm worried about...
I have returned.
Welcome home!
Thank you for doing the shopping
and walking Mochita!
My pleasure.
Oh, you picked out the daikon radish
correctly and everything!
Yes!
I'll never mistake squid for it again.
You mixed up daikon radishes and squid?
When it comes to normal
conversations like this,
I have no trouble talking to her.
Maybe it really was
some kind of Christmas magic,
just like Riko said?
Oh, yeah!
Ms. Yuki, I'm going to ask you some questions,
so answer with "yes" or "no," okay?!
Wha... Hey! Wait!
Question 1. Does Big Brother
physically touch you?
Yes.
One question in, and I'm already mortified!
Question 2. Does Big Brother praise you often?
Yes.
Question 3. Does Big Brother actively
initiate conversation with you?
Yes.
Question 4. Does Big Brother
help you when you're in trouble?
Yes.
Riko
Last one! Question 25.
Has Big Brother ever told you he likes you,
outside of a love confession?
Yes! Just the other day on Christmas.
What...
Ms. Yuki?!
There's a 196% chance that you both
have feelings for each other!
I have no regrets for the life I've led!
Don't kick the bucket over a misunderstanding!
Ms. Yuki! The key to enjoying the kotatsu...
is to stretch your legs out under it.
My legs...
Like this?
Yep, just like that!
Your legs sure are long!
So this is a kotatsu...
It's warm, and a lot of fun.
I know, right? I love them!
We don't have one at home,
so it's been a while since
I've used one or had hotpot on one!
And I have you to thank, Ms. Yuki.
Before, there wasn't enough
space here to set it up,
because Big Brother used to fill the house
with mess to spite our dad.
To spite him?
Sh-Shut up!
Oh? Did I say something I shouldn't have?
Never mind.
I can't admit that I just don't want Ms. Yuki
to find out I used to be a total brat!
I bet you just didn't want me to tell
Ms. Yuki about your childish side!
Riko!
Here I am, tormented with worry,
and she's running her mouth without a care...
He's just trying to look cool
in front of you, Ms. Yuki!
Ponzu
Thanks to you, I'm feeling
extra self-conscious now!
Such misdeeds can only be met
with divine punishment!
And I snorted so hard, the milk
came spurting right out of my nose!
Take this!
So Tsujioka, who sits next
to me, lent me a rag,
Huh?
and I scrubbed the heck out of that desk.
Then the clay eraser stuck to it.
She's not reacting to it at all.
Oh, but it was no ordinary clay eraser.
We worked together as a class to make them
by collecting everyone's leftover clay shavings.
There are three of them,
named "aw," "kaw," and "ard,"
and we totally had a blast, but...
Oh...
Huh?
What?
What's going on, you two?
Oh... Um...
Uh, I'm really sorry!
Huh?
It's quite all right.
What, what?
Is this some secret language between you?
Oh! Does it mean "I love you"?!